James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
  - Speeches, Series 4: 1981-2006
    - Military aviation, Embry Riddle Aeronautical University, November 6, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Arizona and Sonora: Building a Golden Age, Promotion of Industry in Sonora, November 9, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Jokes for ROTC dining, November 13, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Greetings to conference, National Association of Development Companies, November 20, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Remarks, Navy League of the United States, November 20, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Legislative update, Pima County Republican Club, December 1, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Remarks, Committee for Production Sharing, December 10, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Tucson Committee on Foreign Relations, December 10, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Striving for Excellence, ITT Technical Institute commencement, December 12, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Legislative update, Rotary Club, December 30, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Big Sisters Group of the Haven, President's Volunteer Action Awards, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Current Banking Issues, ca. 1987 (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - You Gotta Know the Territory, ca. 1987 (Box 112, Folder 38)
    - Underground contractors, January 6, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 39)
    - Big Brothers/Sisters, January 11, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 40)
    - State of the District 1988, Tucson Trade Bureau, January 14, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    - Outline remarks, Desert Lutheran Church, January 17, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 42)
    - The Wars Powers Resolution: Who's in Charge Here?, January 20, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 43)
    - Douglas Industrial Appreciation night dinner, January 23, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 44)
    - Let's Negotiate a United States-Mexico Free Trade Agreement, January 27, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 45)
    - Inaugural banquet, Southern Arizona Builders Association, January, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 46)
    - Lincoln Day dinner, Santa Cruz County, February 11, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 47)
    - Climb a Mountain, Conquer Cancer, February 13, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 48)
    - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1986, Arizona Wine Growers Association and the University of Arizona, February 27, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 49)
    - United States-Mexico Free Trade Agreement: Building a Partnership for the 21st Century, Mexico City Conference of the Border Trade Alliance, February 29, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 50)
    - The ITC Report: Maquiladoras Help United States Workers, March 9, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 51)
    - Notes for speech, Air Conditioning Contractors of America, March 12, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 52)
    - Wright Flight PSA, March 12, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 53)
    - Financial aid, Financial Aid Forum, March 19, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 54)
    - Talking points: Arizona and California water, Nathan Rosenberg for United States Congress/Orange County, March 28, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 55)
    - Talking points: Outlook for Agriculture, National Ag-Chem Credit conference, April 7, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 56)
    - Talking points: Southern Arizona Environmental Management Society luncheon, April, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 57)
    - Mark-up Salt River Indian Settlement, Central Arizona Irrigation District, May 13, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 58)
    - Making it a Success, the Alpha Delta Nu Transportation Fraternity, May 16, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 59)
    - Answering the mail, Sierra Vista 1200 Club, May 20, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 60)
    - The Border Mentality and What to Do about it, Council of the Americas Border Development conference, May 20, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 61)
    - Remarks, Memorial Day, May 30, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 62)
    - Announcement speech, Kolbe supporters (Media), June 6, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 63)
    - United States-Mexico Relations: Building a Golden Age, 63rd Annual Conference of the American Economic Development Council, June 6, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 64)
    - The Debate rages on, El Presidio Chapter Daughters of the American Revolution, June 9, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 65)
    - Talking points: Medicare malpractice, Doctor's Town Hall, June 17, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 66)
    - Answering the mail, Tucson Republican Women's Club, June 20, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 67)
    - Notes for NARFE speech, June 20, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 68)
    - American Hellenic Educational Progressive Association, June 23, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 69)
    - The Wharton Study: Maquilas Save United States Jobs, June, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 70)
    - Remarks, 1st Assembly of God, July 3, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 71)
    - Congressional reform, Pima County Republican Club, July 5, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 72)
    - Talking points, Regional Reporters Association, July 8, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 73)
    - Thunder Mountain Republican Women, July 19, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 74)
    - Maquiladoras: "Twin Plants", shared prosperity, July 21, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 75)
    - Comments before the Arizona School Business Officials Association, July 22, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 76)
    - Sahuaro Christian Church, August 23, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 77)
    - Base closure legislation and possible on Southern Arizona, August 24, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 78)
    - Republican election, Pima County Republican Women's Club, August 25, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 79)
    - Talking points, Arizona Subcontractors Association, August 25, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 80)
    - Talking points, Vietnam Veterans America meeting, August 25, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 81)
    - Pantano Optimists Club, August 26, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 82)
    - Dedication of Faraway Ranch, August 27, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 83)
    - Remarks, Minorities and small business, September 2, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 84)
    - The Important Role of the Foster Parents: A National Perspective on State of Children and Families, September 17, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 85)
    - Is the Sky Falling over Tucson?, Apics, National Association of Contract Managers, 9-11, September 20, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 86)
    - Notes for NARFE speech, October 10, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 87)
    - National Outlook, Arizona Association of Industries, October 11, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 88)
    - Rural Economic Development in Southeast Arizona, Benson Rotary Club, October 11, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 89)
    - Tapestry for Tomorrow, Arizona Association for Gifted and Talented Children, October 14, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 90)
    - Principles and Pragmatism: Minority Business Development in Tucson, Arizona, Tucson Minority Business Development Center, October 19, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Remarks, American Gas Association meeting, October 24, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Affordable housing, October 25, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Remarks, Rural Health issues, Catastrophic health care, Insurance, October 25, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Villa Campana, October 25, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Legislative highlights of the 100th, Society of Logistical Engineers, October 26, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Remarks for AMRAAM rollout, Hughes Aircraft, October 26, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Debate with Terry Goddard, October 31, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Manufacturing Offshore: Is the Maquiladora Program a Short Term Tactic for Industry or a Long Term Strategy for Increasing Competitiveness?, Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico, November 2, 1988-November 10, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Jim Kolbe's personal naval experience, Marine Corps Ball, November 5, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Talking points, Forest Service Permittee meeting, Sonoita, Arizona, November 14, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Talking points, Closing Remarks, Procurement Conference, November 18, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Economic Growth as International Trade in the Western United States: The View from Arizona, the Financial Post Symposium, November 22, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Public Service Announcement Organ donation, Arizona Kidney Foundation, November 29, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Talking points, National/State local election, Pima County Bar Association, November 29, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Talking points, CAPA/SAWRA Meeting, November 30, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Memories of 4H and lessons learned, National 4H Alumni winner of 1988, December 1, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Youth in Poverty: the Risks to our Future, Arizona Community Action Association Annual conference, December 2, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Remarks to Maricopa County Republican Chairman, December 3, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Remarks, Committee for Production Sharing 12th Annual Meeting, December 6, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Mexican Debt and Restructuring, Background and the current situation, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - The Speech, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - The North American Free Trade Agreement: A Goal for Today and Tomorrow, ca. 1988 (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - United States-Mexico Relations, Trinity Presbyterian Church, ca. 1988 (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - Indian housing, January 10, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - Nogales Rotary, January 12, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Do Quality and Cuts Mix: the Congressional Perspective, American College of Eye Surgeons, January 14, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 27)
    - Talking points, Tucson Chamber of Commerce International Trade Committee, January 18, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - The Nuts and Bolts of Governing, Elected Officials Forum, January 25, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 29)
    - Beyond Survival, State of the District, Tucson Trade Bureau, January 26, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 30)
    - Arizona economy, Association of General Contractors, January 27, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 31)
    - Looking Back, Looking Forward, Pima County Republican Club, February 14, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 32)
    - Triad presentation, Scottsdale, Arizona, February 14, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Navy ROTC, University of Arizona, February 15, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - Looking Back, Looking Forward, Yuma County Lincoln Day dinner, February 17, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - Arizona FFA Field Day, March 3, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - War on Drugs, Great Decisions Group, March 3, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - Cleaning up our House: Congressional Reform, Scottsdale Rotary, March 6, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 38)
    - Talking points for Navy retirement ceremony, March 11, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 39)
    - Looking Forward, Looking Back, Sun City Republican Club, March 27, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 40)
    - Cleaning up our House: Congressional Reform, Green Valley Rotary Club, March 28, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 41)
    - Issues Affecting Water and Water Treatment, Conference on Water and Wastewater Policy in Rural Arizona, March 30, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 42)
    - Legislative round-up, Kiwanis Horizon, March 30, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 43)
    - Cleaning up our House, Phoenix Chamber of Congress, April 7, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 44)
    - The Internationalization of Business: the Role of Government and Business in a Global Economy, International Association of Students in Economic and Commerce, Arizona State University, April 8, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 45)
    - Remarks on Tucson's economy, Northwest Regional Banking Center, Interwest Bank, April 10, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 46)
    - Arizona's Business Climate: How do we Compare?, Arizona Association for Industrial Development, April 14, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 47)
    - Celebration of life, Pima Council on Aging, April 14, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 48)
    - Doing Well by Doing Good, University of Phoenix, April 20, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 49)
    - SCIP Divestiture meeting, Phoenix, Arizona, April 20, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 50)
    - Education/Drop out problems, Mesa Associate for Hispanic Citizens, May 5, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 51)
    - Remarks, San Pedro Riparian National Conservation Area Dedication Ceremony, May 6, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 52)
    - Whose Principles- Thought on Arizona Direction, Mainstream Republican Forum, Phoenix, Arizona, May 13, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 53)
    - Rounding up Tourism and Fattening up the Economy, Metropolitan Tucson Convention and Visitors Bureau, May 15, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 54)
    - Statement on Mexico's New Foreign Investment Rules, May 17, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 55)
    - Confusion and Temptation: Environmental Problems on the United States/Mexico Border, Southern Arizona Environmental Management Society, May 19, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 56)
    - Springerville Airport dedication, May 20, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 57)
    - Yours is the Future: Promise of Threat, Sahuarita High School, May 25, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 58)
    - Yours is the Future: Promise or Threat (2nd version), Nogales High School graduation, June 2, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 59)
    - Talking points for NAACP speaking engagement, June 3, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 60)
    - Remarks, The Orme School graduation, June 3, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 61)
    - Talking points, United States-Mexico Chamber of Commerce, June 15, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - A Gamble for Peace, Air Force Association, June 16, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy in a Changing World, Fort Huachuca, I.S.C., June 17, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Building a Golden Age, Border Trade Alliance planning meeting, Loew's Ventana Canyon, Tucson, Arizona, June 19, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - SRP Political Involvement Committee, June 30, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Views on Press/Politics, Professional Journalist's Society, June 30, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Doing Well by Doing Good, Boss Group, Apache Junction, Arizona, July 7, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Talking points: Catastrophic care, Army Air Force Exchange Service Retirement Employees Association, July 10, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Ethics in Public Life, Naval Institute conference, August 9, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Talking points catastrophic care, Fountains at La Cholla, August 24, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - First amendment, Town Hall, August 25, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Remarks, The Fleet and Industry, Naval Institute Conference, September 8, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Talking points, Drugs, Pathfinders Republic Women's Club, September 15, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - The Economy and Economic Policy in the 90's: The Role of Government and Business in a Global Economy, National Association of Personal Finanical Advisors Western Regional Tucson Conference, September 15, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - The Internationalization of Business: the Role of Government and Business in a Global Economy, International Association of Students in Economic and Commerce, University of Arizona, September 15, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Notes, National Association of Letter Carriers Visit, September 16, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Remarks, 4-H, September 16, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Thoughts from a Desert Rat, National Audubon Society, Tucson, Arizona, September 16, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Remarks, The Environment is Your Business Conference, September 18, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Surviving in the 1990's, UNISYS, September 18, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Tree of Life Award, National Jewish Fund, September 24, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Public Service Announcement, Walter Douglas Elementary School, September 26, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Pragmatism, Minority Enterprise Development Awards Dinner, September 29, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - The Privatization of Space, Tucson, Arizona, October 2, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Remarks, The Pimeria Alta National Monument, October 11, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Arizona Family Day Care conference, October 14, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Remarks, Dining out, 868th tactical missile training group, October 14, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Getting involved, October 19, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - A Few Thoughts about Science, Math and Education, American Chemical Society, November 4, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Clean air, Car Dealers meeting, November 6, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - Trip behind the Iron Curtain, Arizona Farm Bureau, November 10, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 31)
    - Congress review speech, November, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 32)
    - Letter carriers, Review of 101st Congress, December 4, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 33)
    - Statement, International Trade Commission, Phase 1 Hearing, Mexico 332 Investigation, December 5, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 34)
    - Educating for Technological literacy, December, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 35)
    - "The New Mexican Revolution", ca. 1989 (Box 114, Folder 36)
    - Philippines, January, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 37)
    - Voices of Freedom, State of the District Address, Downtown Rotary Club, January 10, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 38)
    - Statement, Commission for the Study of International Migration and Cooperative Economic Development, Sante Fe, New Mexico, January 22, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 39)
    - Voices of Freedom, Green Valley Chamber of Commerce, January 24, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 40)
    - Voices of Freedom, Kiwanis Club of the Desert, February 2, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 41)
    - Talking points on Central America, Great Decisions meeting, February 13, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 42)
    - Community Association Institute, February 14, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 43)
    - Lincoln Day dinner, Graham County Republicans, February 17, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 44)
    - What Goes on Here?, Green Valley R.O.A., February 21, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 45)
    - Remarks at Dedication of Nogales International Sewage Treatment Plant, March 2, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 46)
    - Talking points, Hot issues before Congress, Tucson Trade Bureau, March 2, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 47)
    - Members of the National Public Lands Advisory Council and Representatives of the Nature Conservatory, March 23, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 48)
    - Announcement of candidacy for reelection, April 9, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 49)
    - Talking points, Sisters Kathleen Foundation, April 10, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 50)
    - Notes for Arizona Coalition on Aging speech, April 11, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 51)
    - How to Do Business with the Federal Government, May 3, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 52)
    - Budget deficit/resolution, Chamber of Congress Press conference, May 4, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 53)
    - Opening the Door for Black Business, Black Business Exchange Group, May 4, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 54)
    - Talking points, United States-Mexico Trade, Phoenix Chamber of Commerce Board Retreat, Tucson, Arizona, May 4, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 55)
    - Prospects for United States-Mexico Trade Relations, International Trade Commission field hearing, Tucson, Arizona, May 8, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 56)
    - Cochise College commencement, May 11, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 57)
    - Silent Voices of Freedom, Memorial Day, May 28, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 58)
    - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base Environmental Impact Statement, Scope meeting, May 22, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 59)
    - Goals and means and the new Republican paradigm, Pima County Republicans, May 29, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 60)
    - Keynote Address, Air Force Association annual meeting, May 29, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 61)
    - Talking points: United States-Mexico trade, St. Philips Episcopal Church, June 3, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 62)
    - Old Crows of Sierra Vista, June 15, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 63)
    - 1200 Club, Sierra Vista, Arizona, June 15, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 64)
    - Hughes Aircraft Company, July 9, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 65)
    - Talking points and background information: Legislative update, Society of Human Resource Management of Tucson, July 9, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 66)
    - Congressional update, National Society of Fundraising Executives, August 10, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 67)
    - Environmental concerns and issues along the Arizona-Sonora border, August 10, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 68)
    - Future of International Business, International Association of Students in Economics and Commerce conference, August 15, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 69)
    - Martin Luther King Day, August 15, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 70)
    - Congressional update: Apartment and house industry, August 16, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 71)
    - Statement of Kolbe United States Air Force hearing draft environmental impact statement proposed closure of Myrtle Beach Air Force Base, South Carolina, August 22, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 72)
    - Symington for Governor headquarters, September 4, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 73)
    - Arizona space initiative, September 20, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 74)
    - USS Lexington (CU 16) Sailors annual reunion, October 12, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 75)
    - Mexico-United States Free Trade Agreement: New Light from the New World, Border Trade Alliance, University of Arizona Mexican American Studies and Research Center, October 12, 1990-October 16, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 76)
    - Combined Federal Campaign Fort Huachuca, October 22, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 77)
    - 1200 Club of Sierra Vista, October 27, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 78)
    - Defense Industry prospects in the 90's: A View from Capitol Hill, National Contract Management Association joint meeting, Tucson, Arizona, November 5, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 79)
    - Remarks, University of Arizona College of Nursing, November 5, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 80)
    - United States-Mexico Free Trade Agreement: A View from Congress, Asia Wall Street Journal conference, November 19, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 81)
    - Education speech to Phi Delta Kappa, Sierra Vista, Arizona, November 26, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Mexico-United States Free Trade Agreement: New Light from the New World, Cross Border Manufacturing tour, November 28, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Solid Waste Management: Planning for the Future, Waste Management conference, Sierra Vista, Arizona, December 7, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Medical issues, Current events, Southern Arizona Anesthesia Association, December 10, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Carondelet Rehap Expo '91, American with Disabilities Act, ca. 1990 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - The North American Free Trade Agreement, 1990-1991 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - State of the District, Downtown Rotary Club of Tucson, January 16, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Health, American Pastorial Counsellors, January 17, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - From the Yukon to the Yucatan: Creating a New Vision for Trade in North America, February, 1991-March, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Remarks before the 1991 Maricopa County Board of Supervisors Chairman's conference, March 8, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Good Walls Do Not Make Good Neighbors: The Case for Free Trade with Mexico, Congress for Tomorrow, Princeton, New Jersey, March 14, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Talking points on the Persian Gulf, Arizona Pest Control Association, March 22, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Remarks, Sheriff's Auxiliary dinner, March 23, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - The Probable Economic Effect on United States Industries and Consumers of a Free Trade Agreement between the United States and Mexico, United States International Trade Commission hearing, Phoenix, Arizona, April 8, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Lessons from the Alamo, The Case for Free Trade with Mexico, The San Antonio conference on Mexico: Strategy Session on the North American FTA, San Antonio, Texas, April 11, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Tucson Optical Society, University of Arizona Optical Science, April 15, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - The North American Free Trade Agreement: Opportunities for Hispanic Business, April 17, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Farm the Yukon to the Yucatan: Creating New Vision for Trade in North America, Tucson 2000, April 19, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Talking points, What is Fast Track, What Does the North American Free Trade Agreement Mean to Tucson?, April 19, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 19)